# Wynne Edwards

# Graduate Developer

Makhanda, South Africa

wynnee02@gmail.com

**C** 0713610524

github.com/wynne-edwards

in linkedin.com/wynne-edwards

wynne-edwards.com

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

A bit about me: I am keenly interested in programming, data and, more specifically, data visualisation. I like building, whether it be a tool for navigating data or building a website to show off some learnt skills. I enjoy that I can create something to make a task or experience better. I've also discovered that I work best in a team environment, where I can quickly share ideas and iteratively respond to feedback from other members much faster than if I were on my own.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Rhodes University **2**

BScH (Honours) in Computer Science 01/2024 – present | Makhanda, South Africa

#### Rhodes University 2

BSc Computer Science & Information Systems

2021 - 2023 | Makhanda, South Africa



#### **Programming & Project Management**

(In order of experience)

- Java, Python, C, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Google Scripts
- SQL, Tableau
- SDLC

#### Personal Skills

- Hard Working & Problem Solver
- Continuous Learning
- Responsible, Dependable & Resilient
- Communication & Teamwork

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Rhodes University 🛮

Student Technician

02/2021 - Present | Makhanda, South Africa

Maintained student computers by providing comprehensive support, including virus removal and software assistance.

Reference: b.gerber@ru.ac.za 🛮

#### Singular Systems 2

Internship

06/2023 - 07/2023 | Cape Town, South Africa

Reference: JSpringer@singular.co.za 🛮

#### **Emerald Consulting**

Part Time (Student) Developer

07/2021 - 03/2022

Developed Smartsheets to Google Calendar system. Managed individual employee calendar entries from a unified database.

Reference: hanri@e-c.co.za 🛮

### **♣** PROJECTS

#### Website Creation

Design and Development of Personal Websites Including:

- Level Up Merch Website
- Emerald Consulting Website
- Personal Website
- Scrim Management Discord Bot

## **CERTIFICATES**

**NVIDIA CUDA Python** ☑ — Fundamentals of Accelerated Computing with CUDA Python

#### AWARDS

#### **Systems Development Project Award**

Rhodes University - Information Systems 04/2024

We (4 people) obtained 2nd Place for a year-long group project involving complete SDLC, including designing, developing and integrating a Digs rating website.

#### **DVC Bursary**

Rhodes University

2024

Distinguished Vice Chancellor Bursary for 2024 in accordance to my Computer Science Honours Degree